[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This salad, which originated in Lebanon, is made from parsley, bulgur, mint, tomatoes, spring onions?", "correct_answer": "Tabbouleh", "incorrect_answers": ["Curtido", "Cobb salad", "Urnebes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Blade trilogy, Jessica Alba stars as Abigail Whistler.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Lucas makes a cameo appearance in Episode 3 of Star Wars as which character?", "correct_answer": "Baron Papanoida", "incorrect_answers": ["Count Vallorum", "Baron Onasi", "Atton Rand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What disorder does Sam Dawson have in the film I Am Sam?", "correct_answer": "Autistic Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Attention Deficit Disorder", "Bipolar Disorder", "Schizophrenia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is best suited for network cable that must run close to electrical lines or florescent lighting?", "correct_answer": "Fiber optic cable", "incorrect_answers": ["UTP", "STP", "UDP"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is used to indicate the medication should be taken with food?", "correct_answer": "c.c.", "incorrect_answers": ["w.c.", "l.c.", "a.c."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the treatment of what medical condition are radishes used in alternative medicine?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver diseases", "Coughs", "Intestinal parasites"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is a fortnight?", "correct_answer": "2 weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["3 months", "4 nights", "100 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The face of the person becomes difficult to recognize 24 hours after death.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2004 movie Dawn of the Dead starred Gaylen Ross and Ving Rhames.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of  conic  section wouyld this yield: y=3x^2-9", "correct_answer": "Parabola", "incorrect_answers": ["Line", "Ray", "Cylinder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie brought Kate Winslet her first Academy Award for Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "The Reader", "incorrect_answers": ["Titanic", "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind", "Little Children"]}]